BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/019
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Code no.820804: California, University of (technical unit) and University Professional & Technical Employees - Communication Workers of America, Local 9119, 1977-2004 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Code no.820805: Polk County FL School Board (teachers) and National Education Association / Polk Education Association, 2000- 2003 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Code no.820806: Dade County Water & Sewer Authority (maintenance, customer) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 121, 1990-2005 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Code no.820807: Montgomery County MD (office, professional & technical) and United Food and Commercial Workers, Local 1994, 1990-1998 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Code no.820809: Escambia County FL School District (clerical) and National Education Association / Escambia Education Clerical/Classroom Association, 1992-2004 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Code no.820810: Montgomery County MD (service, labor & trades) and United Food and Commercial Workers, Local 1994, 1995- 1997 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Code no.820812: Broward County Board of Education (clerical) and Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1994-1998 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Code no.820813: Washoe County NV School District (teachers) and National Education Association / Washoe County Teachers Association, 1994-2003 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Code no.820815: Clark County NV School District (teachers) and National Education Association / Clark County Classroom Teachers Association, 1993-1997 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Code no.820816: Clark County NV School District (educational support) and National Education Association / Education Support Employees Association, 1995-2001 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Code no.820817: Clark County NV (general unit) and Service Employees International Union / Nevada State Employees Association, Local 1107, 1984-2003 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Code no.820820: Clark County NV University Medical Center and Service Employees International Union / Nevada State Employees Association, Local 1107, 1994-2006 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Code no.820821: Oneida County (white collar) and United Public Service Employees Union, 1996-2005 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Code no.820822: Oakland Unified Schools (white collar paraprofessional) and Service Employees International Union, Oakland Service Employees Association, Local 790, 1998-2001 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Code no.820824: Oyster Bay NY (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Civil Service Employees Union, Local 811, 1986-2001 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Code no.820825: Pasco County FL District School Board (noninstructional) (SRP) and American Federation of Teachers / United Service Employees of Pasco, 1996-2005 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Code no.820826: Volusia County Board of Education (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / Volusia Teachers Organization, 1987- 2000 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Code no.820827: Escambia County FL School District (teachers) and National Education Association / Escambia Education Association, 1990- 2003 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Code no.820829: Okaloosa County FL School Board (teachers) and National Education Association / Okaloosa County Employees Association, 2000-2002 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Code no.820830: Okaloosa County FL School Board (educational support) and National Education Association / Okaloosa County Educational Support Professionals, 1993-2003 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Code no.820831: Lincoln Public Schools (teachers) and National Education Association / Lincoln Education Association, 1991- 2002 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Code no.820832: Northshore WA School District 417 (teachers) and National Education Association, 1996-2002 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Code no.820833: Tulsa Public Schools (teachers) and Tulsa Classroom Teachers Association, 1996-2001 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Code no.820834: Santa Clara Valley Transit Authority (operations & maintenance) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 265, 1993-2002 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Code no.820835: Eugene School District 4J (Lane CN teachers) and National Education Association / Eugene Employees Association, 1991- 2002 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Code no.820836: Sweetwater Union HS District Teachers and National Education Association, 1993-2002 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Code no.820838: Essex County NJ (clerical unit) and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1158, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Code no.820839: Metropolitan Nashville Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association / Metropolitan Nashville Education Association, 1997-2006 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Code no.820840: Sacramento County (law enforcement) and Sacramento County Deputy Sheriffs Association, 1989-2002 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Code no.820841: Tulsa City (labor & trades) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1180, 1995-2000 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Code no.820842: Buffalo (police) and Buffalo Police Benevolent Association, Local 7, 1991-1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Code no.820843: Brevard County Board of Education (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / Brevard Federation of Teachers, Local 2089, 2001-2005 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Code no.820844: Brevard County Board of Education (classified) and Professional Association of Teachers, Local 1010, 1996- 2006 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Code no.820846: Multnomah County (multi-department) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 88, 2002-2004 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Code no.820847: Philadelphia Board of Education (blue collar) and Service Employees International Union, Local 1201, 1985- 2008 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Code no.820848: Los Angeles Unified School District (administrators) and Associated Administrators of Los Angeles, 1995-2003 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Code no.820849: Pasco County FL District School Board (teachers & profesionals) and American Federation of Teachers / United Service Employees of Pasco, 1992-2003 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Code no.820850: Los Angeles Unified School District (office, technical, & business service-D) and Service Employees International Union / Civil Service Employees Association, Local 500, 1992-2000 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Code no.820851: Los Angeles Unified School District (operations & support-Unit C) and Service Employees International Union, Local 99, 1992-2000 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Code no.820852: Los Angeles Unified School District (instructional aides-Unit B) and Service Employees International Union, Local 99, 1992-2000 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Code no.820855: Marion County FL School District (teachers) and National Education Association, 1992-2004 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Code no.820856: West Contra Costa Unified School District (teachers) and National Education Association, 1991-2001 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Code no.820857: Knox County TN Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association / Knox County Education Association, 1993-1998 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Code no.820858: Oklahoma City (general nonsupervisory unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 2406, 1997-2003 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Code no.820860: Washington County MD Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association / Washington County Teachers Association, 1993-2003 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Code no.820861: Davis County UT School District (teachers) and National Education Association / Davis Education Association, 2002- 2005 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Code no.820862: Baltimore County (police) (evergreen) and Fraternal Order of Police, Lodge 4, 2001-2005 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Code no.820863: Minnesota Independent School District 196 (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers, 1995-2003 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Code no.820864: Davis County UT School District (classified) and Davis County Education Association, 2002-2005 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Code no.820865: Baltimore County (firefighters) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 1131, 2001-2005 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Code no.820866: Baltimore County (white collar) and American Federation of Teachers / Federation of Public Employees, Local 4883, 2001- 2006 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Code no.820868: Poway CA Unified School District (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / Poway Federation of Teachers, 1994- 2005 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Code no.820869: Broward County (white collar) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1591, 1992-2005 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Code no.820870: Broward County (blue collar) and Federation of Public Employees, 1995-2005 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Code no.830038: Pittsburgh Board of Education (teachers & professionals) and Pittsburgh Federation of Teachers (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Code no.830040: Cherry Creek (teachers-Aurora) and National Education Association, 2001-2003 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Code no.830044: Philadelphia Board of Education (teachers & paraprofessionals) and Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, 1988- 2008 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Code no.830095: Harford County MD Bd of Educ (teachers) and National Education Association, 1993-2002 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Code no.830150: Detroit Board of Education (teachers) and Detroit Federation of Teachers, Local 231, 1990-2006 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Code no.830166: District of Columbia Board of Education (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 6, 1982-2001 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Code no.830173: Buffalo Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association, 1978-1990 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Code no.830174: Beaverton OR School District 48 (teachers) and National Education Association / Beaverton Education Association, 1997- 2003 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Code no.830177: Philadelphia Board of Education (professionals, tech, & reading assistants) and Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, 1994-2000 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Code no.830182: Memphis City Schools (blue collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1733, 1995-2001 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Code no.830188: Indianapolis Board of Schools Comm (teachers) and Indiana Education Association, 1991-2003 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Code no.830189: New York City Board of Education (school lunch-annual) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1987-2005 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Code no.830190: New York City Board of Education (school aides) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1987-2002 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Code no.830193: Cincinnati Board of Education (teachers) and Cincinnati Federation of Teachers, Local 1520, 1996-2003 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Code no.830194: Cincinnati Board of Education (blue collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Co. 8, 1987-2002 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Code no.830196: Detroit Board of Education (cleaners,custodians, food service) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 345, 1978-1994 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Code no.830197: Detroit Board of Education (administrative & supervisors) and Organization of School Administrators and Supervisors, Local 28, 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Code no.830198: Montgomery County MD Board of Education (teachers) and Montgomery County Education Association, 1994- 2004 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Code no.830199: Detroit Board of Education (noon-hr & satllite aides) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 2350, 1991- 1994 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Code no.830200: Long Beach Unified School District (clerical & support) and Service Employees International Union / Civil Service Employees Association, Ch. 2, 1998-2003 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Code no.830201: Detroit Board of Education (clerical & technical) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 4168, 1994- 2003 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Code no.830202: Fresno Unified School District (white collar) and Service Employees International Union / Civil Service Employees Association, Ch. 125, 1993-2000 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Code no.830204: Salt Lake City School District (teachers) and Salt Lake Teachers Association, 1997-2002 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Code no.830205: Milwaukee Board of School Directors (food service et.al) and Service Employees International Union, Local 150, 1992- 2001 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Code no.830207: Newark Public Schools (teachers-clerks) and American Federation of Teachers / Newark Teachers Union, Local 481, 1978- 2003 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Code no.830208: Newark Public Schools (aides-per diem subs) and American Federation of Teachers / Newark Teachers Union, Local 481, 2000-2003 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Code no.830212: Baltimore City public schools (school paraprofessionals) and American Federation of Teachers, 1993-1997 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Code no.830213: Phoenix Union High School District (teachers) and National Education Association, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Code no.830222: Gary Board of School Trustees (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / Gary Teachers Union, Local 4, 1994- 1999 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Code no.830223: Chicago Board of Education (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / Chicago Teachers Union, Local 1, 1995- 2007 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Code no.830224: New York City Transit Authority (buses-Staten Island) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 726, 1994-1998 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Code no.830226: New Haven CT Board of Education (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / New Haven Teachers Association, Local 933, 1992-2003 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Code no.830228: Grand Rapids Board of Education (teachers & related) and Grand Rapids Education Association, 1994- 2001 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Code no.830231: Milwaukee Board of School Directors (education assistants) and Milwaukee Teachers' Education Association, 1986- 1996 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Code no.830233: Oregon Health & Sciences University (nurses) and Orgeon Nurses' Association, 1999-2001 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Code no.830236: Michigan, University of (graduate instructors & staff assistantts) and American Federation of Teachers / Graduate Employees Organization, Local 3550, 1996-2008 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Code no.830239: Columbus Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association, 1994-2008 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Code no.830248: New York City Board of Education (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 2, 1995-2005 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Code no.830249: Michigan State (safety & regulation) and MSCA, 1999-2004 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Code no.830255: Boston Board of Education (teachers, RNs) and American Federation of Teachers / Boston Teachers' Union, Local 66, 1994-2000 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Code no.830256: Columbus Board of Education (classified) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Ohio Association of Public School Employees, Local 4, 1990-2001 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Code no.830257: Manatee County FL Board of Education (parprofessionals) and American Federation of Teachers / Manatee Education Association, 1999-2003 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Code no.830258: Ohio State University (registered nurses) and Ohio Nurses Association, 1999-2003 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Code no.830260: Tucson Board of Education (blue collar) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1998- 2003 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Code no.830261: Rochester NY Board of Education (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / New York State United Teachers, 2000-2004 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Code no.830262: Jersey City School District (teachers) and Jersey City Education Association, 1998-2001 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Code no.830263: New York City Board of Education (Education professionals) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 2, 1991- 2000 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Code no.830274: Douglas County School District 001-Omaha (teachers) and National Education Association, 1999-2003 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Code no.830278: Multnomah CN S.D. #1--Portland (teachers) and Portland Association of Teachers, 1992-1998 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Code no.830280: Seattle School District 1 (teachers & professionals) and Seattle Education Association, 1996-2004 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Code no.830281: Douglas County School District 001-Omaha (paraprofessionals) and Service Employees International Union, Local 226, 2000-2003 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Code no.830282: Jefferson County CO Schools (paraprofessionals) and Jefferson County Association of Paraprofessionals, 2000- 2003 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Code no.830283: Connecticut State (protective services-unit NP-5) and International Union of Police Associations / International Association of Fire Fighters, 1999-2004 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Code no.830299: Milwaukee Board of School Directors (teachers) and Milwaukee Teachers' Education Association, 1992-2001 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Code no.830300: Columbus, City of (general unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1632, 2002- 2005 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Code no.830301: Lansing School District (teachers & related) and Lansing Schools Education Association, 1996-2003 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Code no.830311: Denver School District No 1 (city & county teachers) and Denver Classroom Teachers Association, 1994- 2008 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Code no.830312: Regional Transportation District (operations, maintenance, clerical) and Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1001, 1994- 2003 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Code no.830313: Jefferson County CO School Distr R-1 (teachers) and Jefferson County Education Association, 1995-2002 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Code no.830324: Cleveland Board of Education and American Federation of Teachers / Cleveland Teachers Union, 1993-2000 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Code no.830325: Akron Board of Education (teachers) and Akron Education Association, 1996-2005 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Code no.830331: Spokane School District No 81 (teachers) and Spokane Education Association, 1998-2004 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Code no.830353: Madison WI Metropolitan School District (professors) and National Education Association / Madison Teachers Inc., 1991- 2003 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Code no.830408: Toledo Board of Education (teachers) and Toledo Federation of Teachers, 2001-2004 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Code no.830412: Manchester NH Board of School Committee (eachers) and Manchester Education Association, 1988-2000 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Code no.830420: Minneapolis Public Schools (clerical-technical unit) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Board of Education Employees, Local 56, 2000-2004 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Code no.830421: Minneapolis Public Schools (teachers) and Minneapolis Federation of Teachers, 1999-2003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Code no.830422: Wichita Unified Public School Dist 259 (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / United Teachers of Wichita, 1992- 2003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Code no.830423: Rhode Island Hospital (service & maintenance) and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 251, 1993- 2003 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Code no.830424: Rhode Island Hospital (nurses) and American Federation of Teachers / Rhode Island Federation of Teachers and Health Professionals, Local 5098, 1995-2003 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Code no.830425: Union County NJ (general unit) and International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers / New Jersey Civil Service Union, Co. 8, 1995-2000 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Code no.830433: Providence RI School Committee (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers, Local 958, 2001-2004 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Code no.830442: Boulder Valley School District (paraeducators) and Boulder Valley Paraeducators Association, 2001-2004 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Code no.830443: Boulder Valley School District (teachers) and Boulder Valley Education Association, 2002-2004 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Code no.830454: New York City Board of Education (school lunch room) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, DC 37, 1987-2002 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Code no.830456: Tacoma School District 10 (professionals) and Tacoma Education Association, 1991-2001 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Code no.830457: Illinois, University of (service-maintenance) (Chicago Campus) and Service Employees International Union, Local 73, 1996-2000 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Code no.830458: Maryland (various--units A, B, C, D & F) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1995-2000 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Code no.830459: Maryland (public safety--unit H) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1998-2000 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Code no.830460: Maryland (health care professionals--unit E) and American Federation of Teachers / Maryland Professional Employee Council, 1998-2000 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Code no.830461: Maryland (engineering, scientific, administrative, professional-unit G) and American Federation of Teachers / Maryland Professional Employee Council, 1998-2000 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Code no.830470: Wayne State University (faculty) and American Association of University Professors, 1990-2002 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Code no.830472: Pennsylvania State Colleges (faculty & administrative) and Association of Pennsylvania State College and University Faculties, 1990-2002 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Code no.830474: Lodi CA Unified School District (teachers) and Lodi Education Association, 1996-2004 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Code no.830483: Youngstown (teachers) and Youngstown Education Association, 1993-2003 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Code no.830500: Santa Rosa County School Board (teachers) and National Education Association / Santa Rosa Professional Educators, 1995- 2004 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Code no.830505: Anne Arundel County Board of Education (teachers) and National Education Association / Teachers Association of Anne Arundel County, 1978-2002 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Code no.830522: Anoka Hennepin MN Independent School District 11 (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers / Anoka Hennepin Education Association, 1993-2005 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Code no.830532: Hawaii State University (faculty-unit 7) and University of Hawaii Professional Assembly, 1993-2005 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Code no.830533: Hawaii State University (administrative, professional & technical-unit 8) and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees / Hawaii Government Employees Association, Local 152, 1992-2001 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Code no.830534: Memphis (police) and International Union of Police Associations, 1994-2004 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Code no.830535: Memphis (firefighters) and International Association of Fire Fighters, Local 1784, 1994-2004 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Code no.830536: Osseo MN Area Independent School District 279 (teachers) and Osseo Federation of Teachers, Local 1212, 1995- 2003 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Code no.830541: Des Moines Independent Commercial School District (teachers) and National Education Association, 1992- 2002 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Code no.830553: Montgomery County MD Board of Education (support) and Montgomery County Council of Supporting Service Employees / Service Employees International Union, Local 500, 1995-2005 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Code no.830554: Howard County MD Board of Education (teachers) and Howard County Education Association, 1995-2000 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Code no.830555: Howard County MD Board of Education (educational support) and Howard County Education Association, 1996- 2002 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Code no.830575: Connecticut Community Technical Colleges (faculty & nonfaculty) and American Federation of Teachers / Congress of Connecticut Community Colleges, 1997-2005 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Code no.830579: DecAmalgamated Transit Unionr IL Board of Education (teachers & related professionals) and National Education Association, 1999-2003 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Code no.830587: Orleans LA Parish School Board (teachers) and American Federation of Teachers, United Teachers of New Orleans, Local 527, 2000-2003 (Box 27, Folder 18)